<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<MessageCollection>
<posts>
    <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="2" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:04:21.300" Score="62" ViewCount="4484" Body="&lt;p&gt;Every time I turn on my computer, I see a message saying something like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Your battery may be old or broken.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am already aware that my battery is bad. How do I suppress this message?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5" LastEditorUserId="208574" LastEditDate="2014-12-16T01:47:45.980" LastActivityDate="2018-10-05T23:56:48.997" Title="How to get the &quot;Your battery is broken&quot; message to go away?" Tags="&lt;power-management&gt;&lt;notification&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="2" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:15:30.357" Score="41" Body="&lt;p&gt;Maybe &lt;a href=&quot;http://linux.aldeby.org/get-rid-of-your-battery-may-be-broken-notification.html&quot;&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; instructions will help you to get rid of that message.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Added instructions from the link, &lt;kbd&gt;Alt&lt;/kbd&gt;+&lt;kbd&gt;F2&lt;/kbd&gt;, then type in &lt;code&gt;gconf-editor&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Navigate to &lt;code&gt;/apps/gnome-power-manager/notify/low_capacity&lt;/code&gt; and untick the value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or a single command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;gconftool --set /apps/gnome-power-manager/notify/low_capacity --type boolean false&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4" LastEditorUserId="235" LastEditDate="2012-07-30T13:51:42.147" LastActivityDate="2012-07-30T13:51:42.147" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="3" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="258" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:21:50.653" Score="51" ViewCount="15459" Body="&lt;p&gt;How can I set the Software Center to allow non-root users to install stuff from the Ubuntu repos without having to type in their password?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm fully aware of the security implications, and I am willing to take the risk. Fedora 12 shipped with something like this. (By modifying the PolicyKit configuration, I believe)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="35" LastEditorUserId="10581" LastEditDate="2014-02-18T13:33:55.917" LastActivityDate="2019-11-30T09:19:09.707" Title="How can I set the Software Center to install software for non-root users?" Tags="&lt;software-center&gt;&lt;software-installation&gt;&lt;policykit&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="5" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:23:40.273" Score="23" ViewCount="701" Body="&lt;p&gt;What are some alternatives to upgrading without using the standard upgrade system? Suppose for example that I wanted to upgrade an Ubuntu installation on a machine with a poor Internet connection. What would my options be? Could I just use a standard Ubuntu disk to upgrade this machine? If I already have a standard Ubuntu disk and want to use that, could I do a clean install without wiping data?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastEditorUserId="10581" LastEditDate="2014-02-18T13:34:25.793" LastActivityDate="2014-02-18T13:34:25.793" Title="What are some alternatives to upgrading without using the standard upgrade system?" Tags="&lt;upgrade&gt;&lt;live-cd&gt;&lt;system-installation&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="6" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="12" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:23:41.227" Score="44" ViewCount="31077" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a ubuntu development server at work. It is an old rack server that is located somewhere in the company's dungeon, where nobody ever goes. The only way it can work is as a so-called headless server (i.e. with no monitor/keyboard connected and only accepting network connections).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, if you just need terminal access ssh is more than enough. I, however, would also like to connect to the graphical interface from time to time. At the moment I am using the built in VNC functionality but I am pretty sure this is neither the most efficient nor the most secure way of approaching this issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have done a bit of research on the issue but failed to come to any definite conclusions. I read about trying to forward the X environment over ssh, which would at least solve my security concerns. Can anyone share their experiences in setting this up? Is there any other way that might be worth looking at?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I almost exclusively connect to this server from a Windows machine. I don't know if that might be a problem for some of the methods suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastEditorUserId="424958" LastEditDate="2017-12-10T23:38:29.603" LastActivityDate="2018-07-23T14:20:08.313" Title="How to graphically interface with a headless server?" Tags="&lt;server&gt;&lt;ssh&gt;&lt;security&gt;&lt;remote-desktop&gt;&lt;vnc&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="7" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="3764" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:24:22.550" Score="27" ViewCount="1908" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm taking my be-stickered laptop to a coffee shop tonight for an Ubuntu Hour.  I've let a bunch of local LUG people know about it.  How can I ensure people come away from it feeling like the experience was valuable?  Is there something you've done that was particularly successful?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://wiki.ubuntu.com/Hour&quot;&gt;wiki page&lt;/a&gt; about Ubuntu Hours which is very helpful.  I'm interested in collecting best practices from the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="43" LastEditorUserId="235" LastEditDate="2010-08-22T02:10:58.577" LastActivityDate="2018-06-01T02:51:49.553" Title="How do I run a successful Ubuntu Hour?" Tags="&lt;community&gt;&lt;locoteams&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="0" CommunityOwnedDate="2010-07-28T19:34:40.093" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 2.5" />
    <row Id="8" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="240" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:24:41.037" Score="19" ViewCount="3180" Body="&lt;p&gt;I started with Ubuntu Karmic, and wanted to try KDE. So I installed &lt;code&gt;kubuntu-desktop&lt;/code&gt;. Then I wanted to see how XFCE progressed, so I installed &lt;code&gt;xfce4&lt;/code&gt;. I now have Kubuntu with an XFCE splash and login.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do I (safely) purge XFCE and just have the Kubuntu splash / login screen, or am I stuck with frank-en-buntu?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastEditorUserId="106495" LastEditDate="2013-03-29T05:00:51.503" LastActivityDate="2015-05-29T20:56:09.057" Title="How do I go back to KDE splash / login after installing XFCE?" Tags="&lt;kde&gt;&lt;login-screen&gt;&lt;plymouth&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="9" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="35" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:26:46.273" Score="159" ViewCount="123063" Body="&lt;p&gt;Update Manager is constantly offering me updates (e.g. security fixes, updates from PPAs).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How can I tell my Ubuntu installation to automatically download and install updates whenever they become available?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56" LastEditorUserId="44179" LastEditDate="2014-07-22T19:53:14.377" LastActivityDate="2017-05-31T09:25:43.137" Title="How do I enable automatic updates?" Tags="&lt;updates&gt;&lt;unattended-upgrades&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
    <row Id="10" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:26:53.573" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;You could use &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.ubuntu.com/community/FreeNX&quot;&gt;freenx&lt;/a&gt; instead of vnc. Freenx transmits x-commands (with caching) instead of bitmaps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4" LastActivityDate="2010-07-28T19:26:53.573" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 2.5" />
</posts>
</MessageCollection>